{
    "games": [
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "boisson",
                    "content": [
                        " moist",
                        " junk food",
                        " beverage",
                        " nutritious"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "addition",
                    "content": [
                        " diner",
                        " spakling",
                        " nutritious",
                        " check"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "plat",
                    "content": [
                        " self-service",
                        " waiter",
                        " tasty",
                        " course"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "couverts",
                    "content": [
                        " seafood",
                        " tip",
                        " cutlery",
                        " check"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "client",
                    "content": [
                        " spakling",
                        " recommend",
                        " wholesome",
                        " diner"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "sain",
                    "content": [
                        " tasty",
                        " recipe",
                        " moist",
                        " healthful"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "malbouffe",
                    "content": [
                        " waiter",
                        " junk food",
                        " beverage",
                        " moist"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "moelleux",
                    "content": [
                        " spakling",
                        " junk food",
                        " moist",
                        " healthful"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "serviette de table",
                    "content": [
                        " napkin",
                        " seafood",
                        " healthful",
                        " course"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "nutritif",
                    "content": [
                        " starter",
                        " junk food",
                        " nutritious",
                        " takeout"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "recette",
                    "content": [
                        " tasty",
                        " spakling",
                        " recipe",
                        " tablecloth"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "recommander",
                    "content": [
                        " moist",
                        " recommend",
                        " beverage",
                        " spakling"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "fruits de mer",
                    "content": [
                        " self-service",
                        " healthful",
                        " seafood",
                        " spakling"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "libre-servce",
                    "content": [
                        " waiter",
                        " self-service",
                        " spakling",
                        " spicy"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "p\u00e9tillant",
                    "content": [
                        " cutlery",
                        " tip",
                        " spicy",
                        " spakling"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "\u00e9pic\u00e9",
                    "content": [
                        " diner",
                        " napkin",
                        " spicy",
                        " waiter"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "entr\u00e9e",
                    "content": [
                        " diner",
                        " starter",
                        " healthful",
                        " wholesome"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "nappe",
                    "content": [
                        " waiter",
                        " junk food",
                        " tablecloth",
                        " cutlery"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "repas \u00e0 emporter",
                    "content": [
                        " takeout",
                        " recommend",
                        " waiter",
                        " tablecloth"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "savoureux",
                    "content": [
                        " wholesome",
                        " takeout",
                        " healthful",
                        " tasty"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "pourboire",
                    "content": [
                        " tip",
                        " waiter",
                        " spicy",
                        " course"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "serveur",
                    "content": [
                        " waiter",
                        " beverage",
                        " check",
                        " course"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "sain",
                    "content": [
                        " nutritious",
                        " diner",
                        " tasty",
                        " wholesome"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}